About myself...

I consider myself a designer, not specifically UI, visual, interaction... I design experiences by diving into data and doing research, quickly creating and testing prototypes with users, designing and timing the interactions, and working with the developers to make sure that the output is spot on.

I've been designing for a good few years and I have learnt how to work at a startup doing everything from idea conceptualisation to front-end development, at web development agencies alongside front-end developers pushing code to production, and at large design teams, designing collaboratively, iterating and pitching ideas not only to stakeholders but to each of the designers on the team.

Contact

Email: imalvaronistal@gmail.com

Web: nstl.me

Phone: +44 7761724703

Education

Design & multimedia technologies CEADE Leonardo, Seville (Spain) September 2006 - June 2009

Experience

Barclays Bank (Sept 2015 - present)
Designed and built Rise website.
Designed internal applications for colleagues doing UX, visual and interaction design, and working with a design team and developers in different offices globally.

UVD (July 2014 - Sept 2015)

Led design and helped front-end development on various web applications. Also redesigned and developed the agency's website.

Localgiving (Oct 2012 - July 2014)
Led design and helped front-end
development for the entire website,
and created marketing materials.

Oficina De Arte (Sept 2010-Feb 2011)
As the design intern I designed microsites, print and marketing material. Also helped front-end development.

Freelance (Sept 2009 - Oct 2012)

Designed and developed front-end for many SME websites, including